MkvDrama.net
(This program is intended for mature audiences. It may feature explicit content, violence, and strong language)
(All characters, places, and events in this series are entirely fictitious)
=Love of Silom=
(One month later)
Hello, Captain.
How's it going, Lieutenant?
We found three bodies.
Forensics is doing a preliminary exam now.
But, Captain...
All three bodies had their organs removed.
Just like Por's previous victims.
Por had someone backing him.
Then have the autopsy rushed.
And confirm the victims' identities.
See if they match any missing persons reports.
Yes, Captain.
Mom, I'm off.
- Oh. - Oh, there's food too?
Eat first. Come sit down. I'll serve you. Come on.
- Okay? - Okay.
Aren't you eating, Mom? Let's eat together.
I've already eaten. I ate since morning.
Here, it's still hot.
Mm.
Here.
- You eat. Go on. - Thank you.
I still have packing to finish. The courier's coming at 9 AM.
- Mm. - Eat up.
Ouch.
Got a lot of orders, Wai?
- Mm. - Why not hire more people?
I've thought about it, but let me get through this month first.
You were livestreaming till morning again, weren't you?
Yeah. What else can I do?
Singto's about to start kindergarten.
Expenses are increasing.
Luckily, this school has a psychologist.
Otherwise, he might have been delayed for another year or two.
But there's no fee for a psychologist, right?
Yes, but the money we have is still all used up.
I can't see any savings at all.
- I'll be live streaming again around noon. - Mm.
Then get some sleep today. I'll take Singto to school.
Don't you have class?
I do, but I can drop him off first.
Really?
Okay, thanks. But this evening,
I'll pick him up myself.
- Okay. - Singto.
You're going to school with Dad today.
Going with Dad today, okay?
Come on, eat your food. Hurry up.
Eat first so we can get going, okay?
- Open up. - Oh, that's a big bite! Well done!
- Well done. - Show-off.
Such a show-off. I told him back then, but he wouldn't listen.
Hey, let you know
Who his real parent is.
Right, Singto?
Right?
- Right? - Right.
- Eat up. - One more big bite?
One more big bite? Just one more?
Hello. Well done, Singto.
Wai will pick him up this evening, okay?
Understood. Come on, let's go to class.
- Bye-bye. - Say bye to Dad first.
Bye-bye.
Singto, come play with me.
(Mind)
Hello, Mind.
Where are you? You're not at campus yet? I haven't seen you.
I stopped by to drop Singto off at daycare. I'll hurry over.
Okay.
Singto talks to his friends more.
Even if he's not fluent yet,
He's still trying to communicate in his own way.
Singto is making good progress, though he's still a bit behind other kids.
If he keeps opening up, he'll definitely catch up.
And eventually, he'll be speaking normally like the other children.
Thank you so much, for always looking out for him.
Actually, you should tell Mr. Wayu and Ms. Wai, Captain,
That you're the one who's always helping out.
Their family should be thankful to you.
Please keep helping to encourage Singto with his pronunciation.
Help him feel more confident when he speaks.
So he knows he's getting better every single day.
Of course.
Thanks a lot for taking care of all this.
When Singto can speak,
- I owe you big time. - Hmm.
You're just like Rose said, really.
How so?
You even hired me to stay close and look after your ex's nephew.
Why are you putting yourself through this?
Why not just get back together and settle it once and for all?
Has anyone ever told you this?
Watching over him from a distance like this, without letting him know,
Is not cool. It's just sad.
I'm just doing what I said I would.
I told him I'd look after Singto. That's all.
Yeah. Everyone knows what you should do.
But you won't do it.
I'm heading back to the kids. You should get back to work.
- Thanks. - Mm.
Dad cried.
What?
Did Dad cry?
It's okay.
Singto, you have to be a good boy, alright? Hmm?
You have to be strong.
Okay?
You have grown a lot since the last time I saw you.
You're talking more too. Hmm?
Oh.
Ouch.
- Mind, hey, did the cutter cut you? - Yeah.
Mind, I told you I could handle it. But you had to butt in anyway.
You're complaining even though I came to help?
Who told you to help till you got yourself hurt?
Hey, look at this.
- Whoa, my model is stained with blood. - Oh.
Worry about me, not the model.
I am worried.
But if you're going to help, be more careful, okay?
Next time, just sit still, that's enough.
Keep pressure on it for now.
Come on.
Aww, what a sweet model cutting!
Should I make this your relationship reveal clip?
Sweet.
We're just friends.
Hmm.
What?
That's enough. You don't have to do it anymore. I'll handle it.
Mm.
I'm heading out first, Wayu.
(Hurry up and come help design my house.)
Wayu, what are you doing?
Slicing. Slicing the model.
- Slicing the model. We use "slice"? - Yep.
Mind.
Wake up. Let's go home.
What else do you need help?
Oh, that's enough for today.
I'll take the rest home and finish it there.
Okay, I'll get you home.
It's fine. You've been helping me cut the model for days.
You should head back and get some rest.
If you feel bad,
Make it up to me.
How to?
Take me out somewhere.
Somewhere off campus.
Oh, but not drinking. I don't want to drink.
I never said anything about drinking.
Just hanging out, like normal college kids.
Okay? Think of it as a break.
Ah, alright then.
Okay, let's go home.
- Let's go home. - Let's go.
You said it already.
Whoa, Mind.
Is jogging a trip now too?
That's news to me.
It's for health, you know.
But a muscular guy like Wayu should be fine, right?
Don't hosts have to stay in shape?
- Wow. - Give it a rest.
I haven't worked out at all since school started, so...
This is what I look like now.
Even like this, you still look good.
Wow, hardcore stanning.
Thanks.
(Don't worry.)
I'll take care of you and Singto.
Wayu.
Want to hit an onsen or sauna? You'll feel better.
Sorry, Mind, it's just...
I'm not really into saunas.
Oh. Then want to grab food instead?
Okay.
- Hello. - Hello.
- You're Mr. Mind, right? - Yes, I am.
Please come this way.
This way, please.
Wayu.
Are you okay?
Hey, if you don't like it, we can change the restaurant.
Ooh, it's okay, Mind.
Just...
I didn't know it was this place, so I didn't prepare.
Even though you didn't prepare,
You look good already.
- Let's eat then. - Let's go.
This table here, Mr. Mind.
- May I change tables, please? - Sure.
This table is fine too.
Yes, here you go.
- Do you prefer this table? - Yeah.
Are you hungry yet?
- A little. - Here's the menu.
- Thank you. - The menu, please.
Thank you.
(Wayu.)
- Wayu. - Huh?
Have you decided? What do you want to eat?
Oh, give me a second.
- Mind, you ready? - Yeah. Here.
Then I'll have the same as you, Mind.
- The exact same? - Yeah.
I'll have Bistecca alla Fiorentina. Two servings, please.
- Of course. - Thank you.
So, what's up with you today, Wayu?
You don't look too good.
No.
- No? - Yeah, nothing's wrong.
- Really? - Mmm.
- Really? - Mmm-hmm.
Are you sure?
- Hey, Mind, did you know? - Huh?
I used to work part-time here.
- Really? - Mm.
So did you know that server just now?
Hmm... But looks like they've got a whole new staff now.
Ah, I see.
Hey, Mind, I told you...
You didn't have to do this. I would've been happy with some street food,
- Noodles would've filled me up too. - Well.
The noodle shop? By campus would've been fine too, right?
I told you, Wayu. I just wanted to get off campus for once.
Mm.
- And what's this, huh? - Hmm?
You got all dressed up and didn't even tell me first.
I always look this good, don't I?
This looks good too. I mean your outfit.
I always dress well, don't I?
True.
- Excuse me, may I serve this? - Thank you.
So? Does it look good?
It looks amazing. And so pretty too.
Let's take a picture first.
- Wayu. - Hmm?
Give me your hand.
Why are you asking? Huh, I'm not a dog.
Come on. Give me your hand.
What? Are you giving me a gift? I'm not taking it.
Can you just pretend you don't know for once?
Nope.
We're just friends. You can't give me a gift. It's not even my birthday.
Yeah.
I know you don't like expensive things, Wayu.
So I made it myself.
- Really? - Hand over your hand.
Come on. Give it here.
Here.
- Wow. - It fits perfectly.
See?
You made this yourself?
Yeah, I took a workshop for it.
I think maybe...
Maybe it's time.
Time for you to finally let go of the past.
And give yourself a real chance to be happy.
Okay?
Well...
I still like Wayu, you know.
The closer I am to you,
The clearer my feelings get.
I guess
I really can't be just friends with you.
But I'm not trying to pressure you.
I just want you to know that no matter what,
You'll always have me.
Mind, listen.
I'm sorry.
I do care about you.
But only as a friend.
I still can't forget Captain, Mind.
And...
I don't want to waste anyone's time.
Thank you for always being there for me.
But...
I can only accept it this way, really, Mind.
I'm sorry.
♪I'll keep loving you until you see the real world♪
♪And realize it isn't always so perfect♪
♪There's still someone like me who could die in your place♪
♪I'll keep loving you until you see the real world♪
♪Where a princess may never find her prince♪
♪Even if you'll never understand me♪
♪Time will show you that my love is second to none♪
(Thank you for being by my side)
- Hey. - Huh?
- Did you see Wayu's latest post? - Yeah.
Looks like he's gone public with someone named Mind.
I saw them tagging each other in their stories.
Helping to work on models,
And even giving each other rides home.
And today they even went out to eat together.
If you still love Wayu,
Then go back to him.
Apologize, and explain everything to him.
Whatever he says, just accept it.
That's better than showing up at my bar drunk every day.
I want to do that too.
You know, I've imagined it hundreds of times.
How am I supposed to apologize to Wayu?
But there's no way, right?
If I were still with Wayu,
My dad wouldn't stay out of it.
And you know what my dad's capable of.
I don't want him getting dragged into it.
He deserves someone better.
Man, your life's like a full-on drama series.
Mm.
So? How's it going?
How's Mint, the minister's daughter?
You've met her a few times now, haven't you?
It's... going okay.
What do you mean by "going okay"?
You should bring up marriage while you have the chance.
I'll talk to them myself later.
- Here's your coffee. - Ah, thanks.
Come on. They've only been dating for a month.
You're already talking about marriage?
Why wait any longer?
We should talk about it now.
Krit's at the age where he should be starting a family.
Yes.
I'll try talking to Mint about marriage.
Good.
And how's that trafficking case of yours going?
You caught the culprit already. Why isn't the case closed?
People are still dying.
I can't close it yet.
Not until I'm sure
We can wipe them out completely.
Oh? And you're sure it's the same case?
It could be a copycat.
Trafficking cases like this have always been around.
The longer you drag this out, the more people will say you're incompetent.
Just close the case.
Before it turns into a problem.
Grandma will take you today, okay?
Mom's busy with work. I'll pick you up like usual this evening.
Papa...
- Hmm? - Papa.
Papa.
Why? Do you miss Papa, dear?
Mm, but don't let Dad hear that.
He might get sad.
Papa is... at... school.
- Huh? - Papa is at school.
Papa is at school, dear?
Did Papa come to see you at school, dear?
Then... Then you should go to school.
Grandma will take you today.
Where's your bag? Here it is. Put it on slowly.
Very good. Now the other side.
- I'm heading out, Wayu. - See you.
Hello, Tai.
Mind just disappeared.
Should I call him, or go find him?
No, don't.
The more you do this,
The more it'll feel like you're giving him hope.
You need to learn to be a little cruel sometimes.
Come on, I've already broken his heart twice. How much crueler do I need to be?
Yeah, fair point.
If I were like Mind,
I probably wouldn't want to see your face right now.
I think you should give him some time and space.
Or...
Are you changing your mind, starting to feel for Mind?
Hey, no.
I'm just feeling lonely.
Normally, he's always around.
And my peers
Are all waiting to graduate. I'm not close with my junior friends either.
Hey, then come to the bar.
Guarantee you won't be lonely.
Let me see first because I have to submit my project.
Not sure if it'll pass or not.
Okay, if you come, just let me know.
Yeah.
Darn, why did I come up here?
Ugh.
- Hey, Wayu. - Hey, Tai, let me feel your muscles.
Haven't seen you in a while. Your muscles seem smaller now.
Yeah. I haven't been working out much.
You're solid as ever, buddy.
Go on, get back out there. We'll talk later.
- Okay, I'm going to perform first. - Yeah.
- Wait here first. - Yeah, hurry up.
- I'm here, everyone. - Hey, Wayu.
You little troublemaker. Haha.
I missed you so much.
Your muscles are crushing my neck.
Oh, sorry, kid.
Guess I got a little too jacked.
- Darn it. - You really vanished on us.
Seriously, though, how's school? You graduating yet?
Come on, it's only been a month. How would I be graduating already?
The beginning's always an adjustment.
And I've had assignments to turn in, so I haven't had much free time.
But whenever I do, I come see you guys.
- Mm. - Aww, man.
You look even more worn out than when you worked here.
Or are you heartbroken over that cop?
Hey. What? Who's heartbroken?
- He, obviously. - He's just busy. Weren't you listening?
- I did hear him. - Hey, take it easy.
Then how about a drink to take the edge off? My treat.
Come on.
No, thanks, Foei. I'm not really in the mood to drink lately.
Then how about going on stage? Since you're already here.
Yeah, just do a set. Nothing serious.
I can't, Foei. I haven't practiced at all.
- I won't make it. - Oh, come on.
You'll manage just fine.
Even if you forgot the moves,
Just show off that handsome face of yours,
And let the customers look at you. That's all you need to do.
Yeah, bro, enjoy.
No big deal. Come dance with us.
- Yeah. - Come on, Wayu, trust us.
Get out on the floor and the crowd will go wild.
Come on.
Wayu!
Okay!
Fine, I'll do it.
Let's invite our guests.
Feel free to garland the boys and tip them.
- From the back, please. - Thank you.
So?
Settle it.
Thank you so much.
- Oh, hello, Ice. - Hello.
If this is your type, Mr. Ice, may I recommend Kenji?
He may look a little nerdy,
But he's caring and attentive.
I'm booking Wayu for 500 drinks.
500 drinks? Seriously?
Wayu.
- Hey, Ice. - How've you been? Long time no see.
- Doing well? - I'm good.
Come on. Have a drink with me.
- Uh, well... - Wayu, just take it.
He booked you for 500 drinks.
Alright then, I'll have Wayu look after you tonight, Mr. Ice.
- Thank you so much. - Sure.
What are you hesitating for? Go on.
- Just a little bit. - I'm coming.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
Need more ice?
- Yeah, a bit. - Okay.
Thank you.
- Come on. Let's toast to both of us. - Sure.
Don't like this drink? You can change it.
- Oh, no worries. - Hey, man.
No.
I haven't had a drink in over a month.
So getting back into it, I'm a little out of practice.
Oh? Why's that? Were you sick?
No, not really. Uh...
I went back to school, so I don't come here much anymore.
Ah, that explains it. No wonder I haven't seen you around.
Guess I'm lucky today, getting to see you.
Wow, I'm lucky too.
You know, Ice, if it were anyone else,
- I wouldn't accept it. - Wow.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
It's alright. You don't have to drink.
Just chatting is enough.
No way. When I take a job, I have to give it my all.
- Hmm. - Then how about this?
Whoever finishes last does a shot.
- You said it. - Mmm.
- Deal. - Come on.
Go!
I win. Shot.
One Ferris wheel, please.
Whoa.
- Ice, you're better at dancing. - Just a little.
Hey, I have to go. My customer's calling.
Okay, see you.
Want to keep this going somewhere else?
Uh...
Hey, be back by 4 AM, okay?
Please.
- Okay. - Sure.
Excuse me, could we get the check, please?
Bottoms up!
Wow. Done already?
Yay.
Wait, Ice. I've got this.
Thank you. Uh... Haha... Oh.
Hey, thank you, bro.
Thank you, bro. You too, bro.
Okay, go.
Mm.
Great. Come on.
Oh, oops.
Oh.
- Hold on. - What's up?
- Hey. - Whoa.
Hold on, Ice.
- This one's pretty good. - Really?
Mm.
Come on, come on! Woo-hoo!
Go, go, go!
(Thai police are dedicated to public safety)
That's enough for today.
Go home and get some rest.
Sergeant.
- Sergeant. - Uh, yeah, sir.
Go home and sleep.
I can handle it, Captain.
Let's call it a day.
In the morning, I'll go follow up with the latest victim's family.
Have them coordinate it.
Yes, sir. But it'll be morning soon, Captain.
You should take care of yourself too, Captain.
I can't.
I'm being pressured to close the case.
We need to find the real culprit, and fast.
But Por still won't talk.
Should we lean on him again? Make him talk?
It won't work. I've already tried.
Let's go.
Captain! Look at this, Captain.
I found a clip of our victim on the dark web.
There are a lot of them, actually. Take a look, Captain.
Can we find out who uploaded it?
It might take a little time, but I'll try.
(Typing codes)
Sigh, Ugh.
Whoa.
What are you doing, huh?
What are you doing?
Help! Someone, help!
- Help. - Haha.
- Help. - Shh.
No one can hear you scream.
Because there's only you and me here.
Hey, who are you?
Hello.
Ice.
You're not getting away from me.
I've played along with your game long enough.
Now it's your turn to play mine.
Ice, get out of here if you don't want to get dragged into this.
Run? Okay.
Can I borrow the whip?
- Sure. - Mind if I borrow this?
Okay.
Ice, um...
If you want the video to turn out good,
I think you should untie me.
I promise,
I'll make sure it's a knockout.
If you want something satisfying,
You'll have to do better than this.
(Emergency number)
This one's better.
Found it.
It's in Malaysia.
Malaysia, huh?
Chainphop has many clients from Malaysia.
Try to find it first.
Arvo, the company's called Arvo.
Arvo.
Mm.
Got it.
Found it.
(Irfan Faruhanan, Malaysia) The owner is Irfan Faruhanan.
(Crown Plaza Hotel Bangkok, Lumpini Park, 4.4 stars, 2682, Five-star hotel)
(First spotted in Silom)
Found him.
Lieutenant.
Check whether Irfan is in Thailand.
Find out how many houses, condos, and warehouses he has.
Wherever they are, get warrants for all of them.
Yes, Captain.
Everyone, gear up. I've got the suspect's location.
Sergeant, call for backup now. I already sent the coordinates.
- Everyone got that? - Yes, sir.
Haha.
Such a good boy, hmm?
- Ah. - Hmm?
So...
If I run, I die. If I stay, I die anyway.
So I might as well enjoy this.
Ice, if you want this to be good,
You should untie me first.
Sound good?
Mm.
You're the first one who I've ever untied.
- I'll make it worth your while. - Okay.
Okay, come here.
You...
You're not getting away from me.
Hey!
You're finished, Irfan.
It's okay.
Hold on. Come here.
- Are you alright? - I'm fine.
Krit, be careful, Krit.
Can you manage? Let me help.
- Are you alright? - I'm fine.
Just a moment. Let's go.
- You okay? - I'm okay.
What should gonna do?
(Directed by Banchorn Vorasataree)
♪Please lead me out of the walls around my heart♪
♪Please let me know that you are my last♪
♪Please wash away all the tears from my past♪
♪And fade them from my mind♪
♪Please change the life of this hopeless soul♪
♪Please make today a reality, not a dream♪
♪Please let this love belong to only you and me♪
♪From now, from now♪
♪Until our very last day♪
♪Of this hopeless soul, this hopeless soul♪
♪Please make today a reality, not a dream, not a dream♪
♪Please let this love belong to only you and me♪
♪From now, from now♪
♪Until our very last day♪
♪Every scar left in my heart from back then♪
♪I can see them slowly fading away♪
♪Maybe it's because you came into my life♪
♪Turning all the darkness♪
♪Into a beautiful light♪
♪Please show me I was right♪
♪To rise and love again♪
♪Please lead me out of the walls around my heart♪
♪Please let me know that you are my last♪
♪Please wash away all the tears from my past♪
♪And fade them from my mind♪
♪Please change the life of this hopeless soul, this soul♪
♪Please make today a reality, not a dream, not a dream♪
♪Please let this love belong to only you and me♪
♪From now, from now♪
♪Until our very last day♪
♪Please lead me out of the walls around my heart♪
♪Please let me know that you are my last♪
♪Please wash away all the tears from my past♪
♪And fade them from my mind♪
♪Please change the life of this hopeless soul, this soul♪
♪Please make today a reality, not a dream, not a dream♪
♪Please let this love belong to only you and me♪
♪From now, from now♪
♪Until our very last day♪
MkvDrama.net